let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "_____ to a rock concert?",
        answer: "B. Have you ever been",
        options: [
            "A. Were you ever go ",
            "B. Have you ever been",
            "C. Do you ever go ",
            "D. Have you ever go"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: " I _____ the champion last week.",
        answer: "A.  saw",
        options: [
            "A.  saw",
            "B. have seen",
            "C.  see",
            "D. seen",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "I love rock and roll. I _____ it all my life.",
        answer: "D. have liked",
        options: [
            "A. am liking",
            "B. like",
            "C. liking",
            "D. have liked",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The Flash’s concert _____ fantastic 3 years ago.",
        answer: "A. was",
        options: [
            "A. was",
            "B. has",
            "C. have been",
            "D. are",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "I _____ all their records since then",
        answer: "D. have bought",
        options: [
            "A. bought",
            "B. buy",
            "C. buyed",
            "D. have bought",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The Flash _____ together for over fifteen years.",
        answer: "B. have been",
        options: [
            "A. are",
            "B. have been",
            "C. are being",
            "D. heve",

        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "He’s my sister’s son. He’s my _____.",
        answer: "B. nephew",
        options: [
            "A. uncle",
            "B. nephew",
            "C. niece",
            "D. bride",

        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: " I run in races. I’m a(n) _____.",
        answer: "C. athlete",
        options: [
            "A. pilot",
            "B. teenager",
            "C. athlete",
            "D. chef",

        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "In my job I wear the latest fashions. I’m a(n) _____.",
        answer: "D. model",
        options: [
            "A. actor",
            "B. professor",
            "C. nurse",
            "D. model",

        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "I serve you drinks on a plane flight. I’m a _____.",
        answer: "B. flight attendant",
        options: [
            "A. cousin",
            "B. flight attendant",
            "C. niece",
            "D. child",

        ]
        
    },
   
]
